Let's go.
(The Fiery Father and Son)
(MINHO goes into a building.)
- It looks like a college building. - I think he's going to exercise.
He should do activities other than just working out.
I can't do anything since they're in the middle of their training.
He's at a soccer field.
(The soccer training is in full swing.)
You don't have to rush out.
Seung Joon, you don't have to rush that play just now.
Get away!
It's overpowering.
He sounds intense.
I can't approach him.
(Hesitant)
He seems scared.
He's very nervous.
Just wait. Hold the spot there.
Wait. Go back!
Wait there.
Salute!
That was sudden.
I've known him since middle school.
(Who is he?)
He's the division commander Yeonsu-gu, Incheon.
Is it over?
(While looking around the field, he carefully steps forward.)
Dad.
(He was MINHO's dad?)
They have the same eyes.
You have his eyes and nose.
Min Seok does resemble his dad.
(Min Seok is MINHO's brother.)
My father and his father are close friends too.
Our families are quite close.
I see. You already know each other.
- When did you get here? - About 30 minutes ago.
I see.
I'll be done in ten minutes.
- He's sweet to his son. - What a sweet dad.
My father is the head coach of Yongin FC in K League Two.
His name is Choi Yun Kyum.
He's been coaching for over 20 years.
He's the oldest head coach in the Korean soccer industry.
- For 20 years? - He's a veteran coach.
My gosh.
He's an experienced coach...
who's gone through all kinds of hardships.
(With years of experience playing professionally...)
(and representing the national team at the 1988 Seoul Summer Games,)
(he transitioned into coaching.)
He's so cool.
MINHO was bound to be athletic.
MINHO must have gotten good athletic genes from him.
(Coached and trained Bucheon SK, coached Daejeon Hana Citizen FC,)
(coached Caykur Rizespor, coached Hoang Anh Gia Lai FC...)_
He's the legend of K League.
(The first coach of Yongin FC, Choi Yun Kyum)
Yongin FC was founded quite recently.
As his son, I wanted to show him my support.
I was also curious how he was doing with the team.
So I went to the field for a visit.
- I'll be done in ten minutes. - Okay.
- Should I... Okay. - I'll come back later.
- You should go. - Okay.
- You got this. - Okay.
Keep running. You have to keep running once you're in midfield.
Go back quickly.
You must get out of it. You'll get surrounded right away.
Just wait. Hold the spot there.
Wait!
(MINHO always showed his fiery charisma while playing sports.)
- He's just like his dad. - I can see the resemblance.
- There's a resemblance. - The athletic genes.
MINHO is fiery like a flame.
Then his father is explosive like a volcano.
I think his father has more explosive energy.
Gather up.
I felt a lot of things that day.
We don't get that many chances to visit our parents...
- at work. - Right.
- That's right. - As for me,
it was my first time seeing my father in action.
I've gone and watched his games before.
But when I saw him on the field,
he wasn't the same guy I knew as my dad.
- Really? - Yes.
He was a lot more charismatic.
Seeing a different side of my dad...
made me very nervous that day.
Was there another team you supported other than Yongin FC?
No, I don't have a team I support in K League.
His father's team is the team I support.
- It's always been like that. - I saw you support FC Seoul.
(I saw you support FC Seoul.)
We went to the opening game together.
I just like K League.
But I don't support a specific team.
I'm sure his father's team wasn't playing that day.
Right. It was against Suwon.
- Then... - I'd go and watch those games.
- I got the wrong idea for a second. - I see.
- You seem very flustered. - No, I'm not flustered.
No.
- I... - He got up from his seat.
There's so much I want to say.
He doesn't know much about this industry, so I'll keep quiet.
- Okay. - Okay.
You guys are going at each other today.
I shouldn't let him get to me, but he's getting on my nerves.
FC Seoul.
MINHO, come over here.
- He's sweet when he calls MINHO. - Come.
I see. Okay.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Well... - Hello. I'm his son.
Today,
I'm just stopping by to watch you train.
You guys are training really hard.
I brought a coffee truck with me today.
- Have some coffee on your way out. - That's good.
- He seems proud. - Enjoy your dinner.
- He's smiling. - Okay.
- Great work, everyone. - Thank you.
Good luck.
(Turning back)
Grab a cup of coffee on your way out.
Okay.
(Swarming out)
- I can see he's feeling proud. - Right.
He didn't know that I was bringing a coffee truck.
- I see. - Okay.
- It's nothing grand. - Okay.
I brought a coffee truck...
- and fruits. - That's...
There it is.
- He must feel so proud. - My gosh.
(Let me see.)
There it is.
(Wishing Yongin FC a victory!)
(MINHO booked a coffee truck as a surprise for his dad.)
(He even prepared fruit boxes himself for the athletes.)
That's a special gesture now.
(Let's go, Choi Yun Kyum!)
(From his son, MINHO)
You should have put a picture of him making a heart with his fingers.
Right.
- But... - It's all letters.
My father doesn't like that kind of stuff.
You should still do it.
If Hyun Moo sent the food truck,
he would've put about 200 pictures of his face.
It would've been right above, "It's a treat from Hyun Moo."
- Right. - This is...
I would've added a picture of me playing soccer.
(The sender is the star, not the recipient.)
How did you prepare all that?
I did it quickly.
- Do you... - Thank you.
- Do you want a drink? - He's happy.
Do you want a drink?
- I should. The truck is here. - Yes.
Give me a non-caffeinated drink.
- A non-caffeinated drink? - Thank you.
Visit us with a coffee truck from time to time.
- I... - Should it be a quarterly thing?
I should make it a quarterly thing. I can come whenever you want.
I didn't come because I didn't want to get in your way.
(Smiling)
You've never seen a coffee truck before, right?
- Have you seen one? - It's my first time getting one.
- I've never booked one either. - Right.
I didn't know. But he was quite happy with it.
- I bet he was so happy. - Of course, he'd be so happy.
I had no idea. He jokingly said I should visit quarterly.
- But if I did, he would be happy. - Of course.
I felt it that day.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Get a drink. - Okay.
(The volcano dad offers drinks from the coffee truck.)
Have a drink before you go.
Please have a drink, uncle.
You're the best.
Is this your drink, Dad? Is this the ade?
Okay.
(The son prepares the straw for his dad.)
- You're preparing that for me. - Yes.
- Thank you. - Enjoy your drink.
(Sipping)
(Approaching)
Who's that?
- Eul Yong's son. - Really?
- Lee Eul Yong? - Seung Joon.
- Nice to meet you. - Really?
- His son is a soccer player too. - I see.
We met when we were young. Do you remember?
Do you not remember it at all? You were little.
You were only a baby. You had just started walking.
Don't get injured. Good luck.
My father...
trained Coach Lee Eul Yong.
- Really? - Yes.
Coach Lee Eul Yong's oldest son...
- is a soccer player. - Yes.
His second son is playing for Yongin FC.
He's a promising player.
- It's a family of soccer players. - Yes, it is.
I see.
You all know Lee Eul Yong, right?
- You don't? - Did you watch the 2002 World Cup?
- Lee Eul Yong... - Everyone knows him.
- Lee Eul Yong. - You all watched it?
- Do you not know him? - Of course, we know him.
The famous Eul Yong smack.
(The remedy for unsportsmanlike players)
(The legendary Eul Yong smack)
(Of course, I know him.)
No, Dowoon. That's not it.
- You have to turn around and do it. - Right.
You must turn first.
People only remember that when he pulled other great plays.
(He had other powerful plays like the smack.)
- Thank you. - Please enjoy.
- Thank you. - Enjoy your drink.
Good luck this week!
- Thanks. - Sure. Enjoy.
Enjoy.
(Smiling thanks to his son)
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I need to get changed. I'll change in the restroom.
- Okay. See you in a bit. - Yes.
- I'll be back. - Okay.
Why are you getting changed?
I always have workout clothes in my backpack.
Not a surprise there.
"Not a surprise there."
Dad.
(He's carrying his all-purpose bag as usual today.)
This is why I brought my clothes.
(When he goes into a restroom with his backpack,)
(he can change into his workout clothes.)
He's truly something else.
Okay. Let's go.
You have the legs of a soccer player.
(As always, he's fully dressed in his workout clothes today.)
- You fit right in on the field. - Your lower body...
Okay. I'm ready!
(My legs feel light today.)
Your lower body isn't ideal for kicking balls.
- What are you talking about? - You know?
- I can kick any ball. - Only your cleats look good.
- Only his cleats look good. - I can kick any ball.
I came to show my support for my father.
But I was on the soccer field, after all.
I thought I ought to kick the ball a few times.
I suggested that we play a casual game.
A game?
It was hitting the goalpost outside the penalty area.
We had to only hit the top bar.
Whoever hits it more will win.
(Only the hits to the top bar will count.)
- That's an original game. - It's not a shoot-out?
They have to hit the goalpost?
People play this game a lot more.
It's a national game, almost.
To increase accuracy?
Every morning soccer club...
- Okay. - plays this game.
We play before we begin or at the end.
We play this game to decide anything like the order and so on.
Hitting the goalpost?
Did your father teach you how to play soccer as a kid?
- Never. Not even once. - That's interesting.
I heard he didn't because he didn't want you...
- to become a soccer player. - Right.
- In case he became a soccer player? - Really?
He strongly opposed the idea.
- Not the idea of becoming an idol? - He wasn't against that.
If he opposed that, MINHO might've become a soccer player.
(Laughing)
- It just couldn't be soccer. - Right, it couldn't be soccer.
- The loser will pay for dinner. - Okay.
His father used to play professionally too.
- I bet he's competitive too. - Right.
- He's as competitive as me. - The competitive father and son.
- How many times will we play? - What?
- How many times will we play? - There are four here.
You must give me time to practice.
You've been kicking the ball before I got here.
- But I didn't. - I didn't either.
- You kicked it here and there. - I only kicked it two times.
(Their competitive side intensifies even before the game.)
You can kick it twice then.
- You can kick it twice then. - I'll do that to warm up a bit.
- But you've been... - I'll just practice once.
working out,
- But... - so you have lower body strength.
- But still. - I don't have lower body strength.
I'm not a professional athlete.
I'm not either.
(I'm not either.)
- I'll just practice one round. - Practice as much as you want.
- I just need one round. That's it. - Okay.
(Stretching)
I can just kick it gently. I don't need to kick it hard, right?
- Go ahead. - Okay.
(He starts practicing amid subtle pressure.)
My gosh.
(The ball flies close to the goalpost on his first try.)
He's good.
(Okay. I got it.)
- I got it. Okay. - Run and get the ball.
- Run and get the ball. - Okay.
(Running fast)
(Laughing)
He's too slow.
(Unbelievable)
Okay. Let's do it right away.
(Flashy moves)
It's been a while since we played together.
(Not paying attention)
Rock-paper-scissors to decide who goes first.
I'll let you go first. Go ahead.
- No. I want to go after you. - After me?
- Yes. Okay. - I'll go first then.
So you're really determined to beat your dad, you brat.
(So you're really determined to beat your dad, you brat.)
I won't go easy on you. You have to give it your all.
- Of course. It's a match. - Right.
He was on the national soccer team.
(His dad is the oldest and the most experienced head coach in K League.)
He's the source of my competitive side.
I've gotten the competitive genes from him.
- He used to play professionally. - I don't think he can beat his dad.
- Right. - But you can't overlook age.
- He's older now. - Right.
(The volcano dad goes first.)
Of course. It's a match.
Right.
(I'm still an active volcano.)
- What? - He got it on his first try.
(Falling flat)
(Laughing)
What are you doing?
What was that, Dad?
My aim is a bit off.
But my ball went in.
Okay. It's my turn.
(The son is up next.)
(Here's what you need to know about me.)
(The living legend of "Idol Star Athletics Championships")
He's the legend.
(Do you think I'm going to lose?)
(You think that's an option for me?)
- It's over. - Okay. It's over.
(Losing is never in the cards for me.)
I think he can do it.
(Getting ready for his fiery shot)
(The ball is getting close to the top bar once again.)
- He got it. - He did it.
(Did he successfully gain the upper hand?)
- Gosh. - Gosh, that was close.
I think he can hit the top bar after a few tries.
He got the hang of it, though.
No, he's doomed.
(Gosh, he's unbelievable.)
- Gosh. - Gosh, that was close.
(I almost had it.)
(Relieved)
(The father and the son both failed their 1st try.)
It's your turn now. Go.
Go.
(I'm done with my warm-up.)
(Zeroing in on the target)
- He got it. - He got it.
- He got it. - He really got it.
He got it.
That was crazy.
- That was crazy. - His shots are a lot more accurate.
(He zeroes in on the goalpost within two tries.)
I was so surprised.
Professionals can zero in much faster than us.
Right. He got it on his second try.
- That's amazing. - How is that possible?
(This isn't good for me.)
I've been playing soccer all my life.
Hold on. That wasn't supposed to happen.
(Flustered)
- Okay. - Just hit it once.
I think I'm going to beat you even if you do.
No way. I'm going to make it happen now.
I can feel it.
I can't believe he hit the goalpost on his second try.
(I'll catch up right away.)
(Focusing all of his energy on his toes)
Gosh, I kicked it too hard.
- Gosh, I kicked it too hard. - Oh, my. What's he doing?
I had too much energy that day.
- Will you be able to sleep tonight? - No.
- Because you lost to me... - No way.
(Hitting 2 home runs in a row)
(This is driving me crazy.)
(You have a long way to go to catch up with me.)
- The last one? - Yes, it's the last one.
(It's already their fourth try.)
- Either I win or it's a tie. - Right.
- It's over if I hit the goalpost. - Okay.
- Gosh. - What was that? Come on.
(He wastes his last chance.)
(Relieved)
Let's take it to overtime.
(I can't lose to him like this.)
(Desperate)
I need to relax more when I kick the ball.
(Exhaling)
It's a nerve-racking moment.
(He's quite serious to beat his dad.)
I was really serious about winning.
You look like that when you eat tteokbokki.
(This is nothing new to us.)
(The last ball to decide their fate)
(Here it goes!)
Gosh, he's doomed.
(Swooshing)
(Sighing)
- Let's go. Thanks for dinner. - No. Let's kick it one more time.
We should kick at least 5 times. Let's kick it 1 more time.
It's the last time. Let's kick it one more time.
- He plays until he wins. - It's a shame to end it now.
(Feeling guilty)
What if he says the last one counts as two points?
(He's about to insist the last shot counts as 2 points.)
- Or 100 points. - You read my mind.
It's a shame to end it now.
You'll never hit the goalpost even if you have all day.
(It's not a shame to end it here.)
(The game is already over.)
This is the last time. I promise.
(Fine. I'll kick it one more time.)
- Gosh. What's up with that? - Okay.
- My aim is off too. - You must be nervous.
I'll get it this time.
- You're in my way. Move back. - What?
Why did you stand in my way?
(He's winning, but he still has to keep the pressure on.)
It's my last chance. Okay.
I must redeem myself with this chance.
It's a match of pride,
not between a father and a son. It's a battle, man to man.
Your father must find you so cute.
(His dad is at ease.)
I'll aim for the top left corner.
(It's time to show him my last fiery shot.)
(Please!)
- What? - No. He doesn't have it.
- He got it. - He got it.
(He ties the game with an extra turn.)
(Giggling)
(Screaming)
He's that happy?
(I said I wouldn't lose.)
- Imagine if he missed it. - He'll lose his voice.
(Dreams come true.)
No one is as competitive as him.
(Is he that happy?)
Bravo.
(Dad, did you see that?)
What's with the gaze?
It's like he was doing a shoot-out at the World Cup.
(It looks like he made the winning goal of the World Cup.)
Let's go into overtime.
- No, it was already over. - Let's take it to overtime.
- You gave me a chance. - That's...
- You can't insist that on me. - My gosh.
- You shouldn't have let me do it. - We should do another game then.
If both of us don't make the shot, it's over.
- The last one? Okay. - Yes.
(It's their final shot.)
(Please fail.)
(The trajectory looks good.)
- That was so close. - My gosh. This is crazy.
(Scared)
I'm getting the hang of it now.
As for me,
I can hit the goalpost if I center my focus beforehand.
- Okay. - Give me some time.
Just gently.
(Smiling)
All right. Look at the spot.
- Here it goes. - I don't think you can hit it.
(No, you're wrong. I'm going to make the shot.)
(Did centering his focus work?)
(It was very effective!)
Yes!
(He beats his dad after relentlessly pestering him.)
You must be so happy to beat your dad.
(MINHO wins.)
(Cheerful)
Gosh, I beat him.
- Fine, you won. - Good for you.
You must be so happy to beat your dad.
(Glancing over)
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
You're the best indeed.
MINHO is the best.
- He's unstoppable. - Yes.
You're so cool.
My gosh.
Something feels off.
It's been a while since he won without any cheers.
- Before and after soccer games, - You...
we used to make this bet from time to time.
- It's the fairest bet. - Okay.
I had never won before.
He hasn't been training for two months.
- No. This makes it clear. - When we played...
- What do you mean? - He let you win.
- He let you win. - Did he?
You could never understand how deeply your father loves you.
My gosh, I finally won. I always lost to him.
(Clueless of his father's intention, the son is happy.)
I finally won.
I easily beat him.
- You beat him? - Yes.
Coach, you have to move the goalpost.
The loser has to move the goalpost?
The players are coming out because he lost.
- Really? - Tell them to move the goalpost.
Hey, the coach is going to move the goalpost.
- Wait. - I beat your coach.
I won, but I'll still move it.
(Chuckling)
(He moves the goalpost while taking all the credit.)
(Cheering)
My body suddenly feels light.
The weather is great too. I'm having the best day.
Okay.
So you'll buy me dinner?
You have to buy me dinner. You lost.
There shouldn't have been a rematch.
(They're bickering as they go to get changed.)
I'm hungry.
You're really off work now.
- You walk out here to get off work. - Yes.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Have a safe drive back. Thank you.
It's still chilly at night.
- Yes. - You have to bundle up.
(Closing)
- Let's make a pit stop... - Okay.
- before we have dinner. - What?
That was sudden.
"Let's play Hit-the-Goalpost again."
Let's go.
(His dad is driving them somewhere.)
Are you getting familiar with the neighborhood?
- Not yet. - Not yet.
- Right. - No.
(Touching his nose)
It's quiet when it's just you and your dad.
And it was just the two of us in the car.
I didn't know what to say to him.
- Do you feel awkward around him? - Do you feel awkward?
Strangely, I feel awkward in the car.
- Really? - Yes, just in the car.
- I don't get chatty in the car. - Right.
- Do you talk a lot? - I...
do talk a lot in the car.
You're different although you're from Gyeongsang Province.
- My dad is an egen-man. - An egen-man?
"My dad is an egen-man."
(Chattering)
That was unexpected.
I've never heard of a father being an egen-man.
So he likes to chat. Is that it?
- Yes, he does. - I see. It's different then.
(MINHO's family is an average family.)
It's the same with every family.
(Looking around)
What have you been doing for your exercise?
- For my exercise? - Yes.
- What do I do? - Yes.
Well, I do a few activities.
- A few activities? - Do you think I work out too much?
Yes, you do.
You won't do HYROX, right?
No, I'm still doing it.
When's the next contest? Is there another one?
It was crazy how he won first place in the HYROX contest.
- He won first place? - He did.
He won first place?
(A full-body fitness program he trained for)
- That's amazing. - Gosh.
I won at last.
(Feeling proud)
Gosh, that's incredible.
(Glancing)
- Let's do MOO-YROX. - MOO-YROX...
Over my dead body.
- I'll never do it... - Hyun Moo.
no matter how trendy it is.
- The age group... - No! I won't do it.
- Hear me out. - Never.
- You compete with your age group. - No.
- You have a shot. - No.
If you just complete the race, you could...
- win third place. - I'll never be able to finish it.
(I can never do it.)
Where are we, Dad?
I didn't know where we were going. I just followed him.
- Is there a table? - Is it a cafe?
- Hello. - Hello.
(He follows his dad into a cafe.)
Do you want me to get you coffee?
- Yes. - What do you want? A latte?
I'll drink a latte.
- A latte? - Yes.
- You'll buy me coffee? - Yes.
Wait. I don't have my wallet.
- Why don't you have a wallet? - It's in the car.
- That's a classic move. - Yes.
I didn't leave it behind on purpose.
Here.
Nice.
(Flustered)
I'm disappointed in MINHO.
I see a lot of rising stars in the field of being a bad son.
Why am I being a bad son?
What's the point of winning first place in HYROX?
You don't spend money on your parents.
- He spends the most money on them. - I won.
- Thank you. - Here you go.
- You're serving the drinks. - Right.
(Pulling the chair back)
- Enjoy. - Okay.
Thank you.
Sit down.
It's my signature latte with barley and coconut.
- What is it? - Do they know each other?
I think they know each other.
(He joins their table.)
Wait. What's going on?
We've crossed paths when I was in Daejeon.
- I see. - I see.
He's the first sponsor of Yongin FC.
(The 1st civilian to sponsor Yongin FC)
Civic soccer clubs can receive...
- sponsorship from local residents. - Right.
- Right. - I see.
He runs a dental clinic.
To promote his dental clinic,
he sponsors the club.
(He's sponsoring the club to promote his clinic.)
In a way, you're meeting your dad's fan.
- Right. - Yes.
His father's fan.
I've heard a lot about you.
- Thank you for coming. - Gosh, don't mention it.
I wanted to introduce my son to you.
His proud son.
He comes to every match to root for our team.
I'll come by and say hello next time.
Thank you.
So you've been rooting for my dad...
- Oh, right. - ever since he was in Daejeon.
- He must feel so grateful. - My gosh.
I'm quite famous as a big soccer fan among my friends.
I used to go and watch a lot of K League matches...
when I was in Daejeon.
He was appointed the head coach of the local team.
I went to watch one of the games. And the rest is history.
(Smiling)
Back then, Daejeon...
was known as the city of soccer.
- It was no joke. - I can see his pride.
(Back then, they were on a winning streak.)
(They achieved the best performance in club history.)
(Elated)
I watched his career growing up.
I always have this image...
of what soccer should be in my head.
- I remember the audience too. - He seems proud.
- He's happy. - About 20,000 people showed up.
You know the vibe from the old days.
They were the good old days. I loved the stadium too.
- I loved it. - Yes.
Years have passed by.
- And I set up a clinic in Yongin. - Yes.
Then he was appointed the head coach of the club.
- Seriously. What a precious bond. - They have a special bond.
- That makes me happy. - I see.
What an interesting history.
Sometimes, I hear things like this. "I'm a fan of Coach Choi."
"That's why I'm rooting for you too."
I feel happier when I hear that.
- That must make him feel good. - He must be happy.
Meeting a fan of my father...
Actually, I'm his son, but also his fan.
So I was happy because it felt like I met a fellow fan.
MINHO, can we take a picture together?
- I'll take it before I leave. - Sure.
- I'll take it then. - Thank you.
Where should we take it?
- The workers... - They're already setting it up.
(He's as popular as his father.)
(Feeling proud)
I didn't know he looked that happy.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Let's get his autograph. - Sure.
(Busy)
I'm old news now that my son is here.
- He must feel good about that too. - Right.
He's proud.
- Thank you for your hard work. - Thank you for your hard work.
- Bye. - Bye.
Okay.
- They're so nice. - Where are they going next?
(They head somewhere again.)
They're totally in full bloom.
Yes.
(Peeking)
(MINHO follows his dad as he leads the way.)
(Looking around)
It's different from a regular hotel.
- Really? - Yes.
- It feels different. - Right.
Is it a dormitory?
The club doesn't have a dormitory yet.
They got him an apartment,
so he currently lives there.
- Welcome. - Okay.
Seriously, there's nothing.
There's nothing. What did you expect?
- I mean... - Isn't it too empty?
- It's too empty. - There's absolutely nothing.
It's so clean.
- I guess he only sleeps there. - He only sleeps there.
(There's nothing more than meets the eye.)
- It's totally empty. - Yes.
(Looking around)
(Is this it?)
A washing machine is over here.
Okay. I see.
- There is a microwave too. - There are home appliances.
There is a fridge. You can cook your meals here.
That's right.
(Let's open the fridge.)
It must be empty.
It's empty.
- There's nothing. - Yes.
(There's nothing.)
You and Mom always make this with a milk carton.
It's a container.
- People did that back in the day. - It's convenient.
- I mean... - Do you sleep on that bed?
- What? - Where do you sleep?
- Here. Yes. - Here?
- Don't you use that bed? - I rarely use it.
(He's curious about every little thing.)
I'm just curious.
Why would you be curious?
I'm curious to know where you sleep.
That's how it is.
The situation has been reversed. When you enter a university,
- your parents check out your place. - That's right.
- Yes. - Your mom does that.
- This is the same situation. - That's right.
At what age did the family members start living separately?
- Us? - Yes.
Since my high school years. I was in 11th grade.
I've lived away from home since then.
- Exactly. - You've done the same.
I've lived away from home too.
- You brought that clock. - Yes.
It was in your room.
- He served in the Marine Corps. - I think it's MINHO's.
I received it during my military service.
It was a present that came with my certificate of merit.
When I entered the Marine Corps,
- my dad wasn't happy. - Okay.
He was like, "Why take the difficult path?"
But I think he's proud that I've served there.
- He always carries that clock. - I see.
(He always carries that clock.)
- You use that clock very well. - Yes.
- Is it convenient? - Yes.
- The numbers are bright at night. - Okay.
(I like that I can see the numbers easily at night.)
(Shall I take a look inside the closet?)
You don't have many clothes.
Don't you need more clothes?
- I only need my workout clothes... - That's right.
- He leads a very simple life. - and a suit.
(Let's see.)
Didn't you wear this...
- for the open match on a media day? - That's right.
- Isn't it the suit we got together? - Yes.
- I think so. - Right.
- I'm surprised that you remember. - Of course. I wear it too.
(Dad and two sons' matching looks)
(MINHO's older brother, Min Seok)
- That's cool. - How nice.
I think we should get another one. Why are you against the idea?
- We don't need another one. - What?
Why do you and Mom always say no...
when I want to do something for you guys?
- We don't want your help. - My goodness.
(Chuckling)
Why not? It's just a suit.
- I have two suits in the office. - Okay.
I have one in the closet.
I find that very fascinating.
My mom asks me to buy her things, but my dad doesn't.
That's good. You should be happy when your parents ask for things.
I'm serious.
Dowoon, your dad must ask for things since he's an egen-guy.
Yes, he does.
My parents go, "We need a new bed."
That's so nice.
It's nice indeed.
It puts my mind at ease.
- That's right. - Of course, it does.
My mom keeps trying to stash cash.
- "Stash?" - "Stash?"
How could you say that, you punk?
Don't say that about your mom. Seriously.
She doesn't need anything.
At every occasion,
- she asks for cash. - Cash?
- That's understandable. - Cash is the best.
That's why you need to keep saying...
that you're struggling financially.
- That came out of nowhere. - My goodness.
- Hold on. Suddenly... - "I don't have any money."
- Keep saying that. - Why...
- Okay. - Why did this take a strange turn?
- Hold on. - Don't call me unfilial.
- You know... - I became so startled just now.
- I can't believe these people. - Seriously.
So this is how people feel when they look at me.
- You know... - I became so startled.
It won't be easy to win this match.
- I'll need to write down this tip. - Even I haven't thought of it.
(I want to buy my dad another suit.)
- He feels uncomfortable. - Yes.
- You only sleep here. - Yes.
My dad kept going, "There's nothing."
- "Why would you visit?" - Dads are always like that.
When I visited the apartment, there really was nothing.
It made me feel more...
It was a bit...
I felt for him, to be honest.
He must be bored and lonely there.
He always gets stressed out in the world of competition.
There's a lot on his mind.
When I think about...
how he spends his time in that empty apartment...
It was...
one of the moments that made me feel a bit apologetic.
"Living here alone must feel lonely."
"I'll need to call him often." I had that thought.
I wanted to visit and see how you were living.
I see.
- Let's go. Let's head out. - Okay.
(I'll visit next time.)
We should fill the fridge.
We don't need to do that.
- Let's make a quick stop. - Okay.
- They'll buy something. - MINHO will buy him something.
- Hello. - Welcome.
I'm looking for sunscreen. Where are the sunscreen sticks?
If you're looking for one for men,
- this is a good choice. - Okay.
- Is it for your dad? - This one is the best.
Okay.
Dad, you never put on sunscreen.
- You... - Is that why we're here?
Yes, that's why we're here.
My goodness.
(Dad, I'm here to buy you sunscreen.)
(For his dad who works under the scorching sun,)
(he wants to give a present.)
It's TAEMIN.
- Is it TAEMIN? - Yes.
(It's good to see him.)
Let's buy TAEMIN's.
- Shall we do that? - Yes.
He's your bandmate.
This one might not suit your skin.
Let's buy two.
- Two are enough. - Okay.
What else do you need? Do you have lotion?
Yes, I do. It's okay.
- Let's buy it while we're here. - No.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
- How about a cleansing foam? - I have it.
- Do you have it? - Yes.
- Do you have lotion? - I have it.
- He has everything. - He says he has everything.
- Hello. - Are you ready to pay?
- You wanted to come here for that. - Yes.
- Please insert your card. - Okay.
- Thank you. Have a good night. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Let's go and eat now. - Okay.
Thank you. I'll use them well.
I realized something that day.
- I just need to do it. - You just need to buy it.
- He doesn't tell you what he needs. - No.
You should visit again and check.
The sun stick might be brand new.
Visit when there's a match and put it on his face.
Do it at the stadium.
- Shall I go in advance? - Yes.
Run to Yongin. That's a good idea.
I'm really hungry now.
- This place is clean and tasty. - I see.
- Hello. - Welcome.
- Is it a gukbap place? - Hello.
Is it a barbecue place?
It seems like a rib place.
Hello.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
(Food gets prepared right away.)
- Marinated crabs. - Marinated crabs?
This place is popular.
The side dishes look nice.
(Glancing over)
Did the owner step outside?
We want to say hello properly.
Sir, please come here for a second.
Let's say hello properly.
Hello.
- He knows this owner. - He knows this owner too.
- He knows all the owners. - I was born in 1990.
- You're a year older than me. - A year older.
- I look ten years older. - No.
You did ssireum back in the day.
- That's right. - Really?
I should've known from your arms...
- and body. - It looks like you've lost weight.
I'm trying to lose weight before my wedding.
- Really? Congratulations. - Congratulations.
- Thank you. - We'll enjoy the food.
- I'll prepare your food quickly. - Okay.
(He brags about his son at every restaurant he frequents.)
It looks like high-quality meat.
- My goodness. - It looks so delicious.
It looks tasty.
- It looks tasty. - It's well-marbled.
(Dinner with high-quality meat)
I should pay for the meal.
- I still make money. - Okay.
A bet is a bet.
- Didn't you bring your wallet? - He'll pay, right?
I'm sure he'll pay this time.
No way.
I won the game of hitting the goalpost, so...
You're reaping the rewards until late at night.
I've bought him many meals.
He must've gone there to eat for free.
(Fiery unfilial son)
(Putting)
I'll grill the meat.
You should do that much for a free meal.
Grill it nicely.
You're paying for it.
It looks tasty.
(Beef gets grilled nicely.)
That's the tastiest.
(Gulping)
(Excuse me.)
- Thank you. - This is on the house.
- Is it cheonggukjang? - Yes.
Nice.
You like cheonggukjang.
- It's the version you like. - Yes.
It has many chilis.
(He fills a bowl with it.)
He and I like the same food.
- I see. - All right.
- Thank you. - Okay.
Try the marinated crabs. You like the dish.
Eat them first.
(He tries his favorite dish, cheonggukjang, first.)
You and your dad know each other's taste.
I find that touching.
It's nice to eat cheonggukjang for the first time in a while.
(The dad and son drink the soup in the same manner.)
I love the soup.
(Picking up a piece of meat)
- Eat up. - Okay.
(Dad, please eat up.)
(He eats the meat his son has grilled.)
Eat up.
(Nodding)
(Impressed)
- Isn't it tasty? - It's tasty.
(The meat tastes even better because his dad is paying.)
The meat was so tasty.
- It's delicious. - Yes.
(He's eating with gusto.)
- Try this as well. - Okay.
(He eats mushroom too.)
Dad, you always said this when I was young.
- When we were in the elevator, - Okay.
you always said that you weren't my dad,
but a middle-aged man from the neighboring house.
- Yes. - You always said that.
- I got fooled as a child. - Why?
You always said that you got me from under the bridge.
I cried about it.
When I was young, I didn't think that I resembled you a lot.
I thought I resembled Mom.
MINHO takes after his mom a lot.
How cute!
(When he was young, MINHO took after his mom a lot.)
Now that I'm older, I definitely resemble you.
In what ways?
- I have your jawline... - Okay.
and eyes.
From the back, you guys walk the same.
- Seriously. - You guys walk the same.
I'm glad that you only resemble the good things.
Do you think I have your competitiveness?
I think you have my competitiveness.
I also hate losing.
But while I don't show it,
you show it with your actions and facial expressions.
With your actions and facial expressions.
(His competitiveness explodes.)
When you lose a match, it shows on your face.
(Upset)
- But I'm worse. - Yes.
(I admit it.)
(Screaming)
I don't know why I make it so obvious.
(Staring)
You exercise...
and influence people in a good way.
(Despite your competitiveness, you're a good influence.)
I think you're going in a nice direction.
I'm not really good at saying such things to people.
I don't do that.
Still, I'm grateful for you.
I'm proud of you.
(You grew up well.)
I'm grateful that you grew up well.
In a sense, you've become...
the pride of the family.
- All of your aunts... - It looks like he's a bit moved.
- love you. - Really?
You're my son.
"He grew up well. You raised him well."
I feel the happiest when I hear such words.
(MINHO, come.)
He's proud of his son.
(He wants to introduce his son who is his pride to everyone.)
You raised me well.
To be honest, he rarely says such words.
I think he was happy that day.
His son came to cheer him on.
It's the same for you.
Many people tell me that you're the coach...
they respect the most.
Many dads tell me...
that you're the best dad.
I hear that very often.
Those words make me happy.
"My dad is cool."
"He isn't all words."
"He shows with his actions."
I feel that often.
- Don't you need to eat more? - No, I'm full.
I ate everything, Dad.
Don't be ridiculous.
I ate a lot today for the first time in a while.
(Clean)
Does Mom know that I had dinner with you?
Of course, she does.
- Shall we call her? - Yes.
She must be curious.
- MINHO. - Mom.
What are you doing?
- Nothing. - Nothing?
Did you have dinner with your dad?
Yes, we had beef.
Well done. Your dad's face became gaunt.
He lost so much weight.
It's because he has many worries.
- Mom. - Yes?
He needs to overcome it.
He should learn how to overcome it from you.
Dad needs to overcome it.
I came here to give him strength today.
Well done.
To be honest, I felt very happy...
throughout the day.
But at the same time, I felt a bit sad.
I thought he'd kick the ball with ease,
but he wasn't how he used to be.
I realized that many years have passed.
Also, we feel happy...
when we're together.
I felt bad that I hadn't visited sooner.
Whenever people ask me...
what kind of a person I want to be,
I always say that I want to be...
someone like my dad.
If I'm doing well,
he praises me continuously.
If I'm clumsy or lacking in any way,
he scolds me as his dad.
It's thanks to him that I've grown well.
To this day, I want to be...
my dad's biggest fan...
and dependable son.
- I enjoyed the food. - Okay.
- It was really nice. - I'm glad you enjoyed it.
I got this dinner since I won fairly.
That isn't true.
- Thank you for the food. Let's go. - Okay.
(The Everlasting Fire That Shines Upon Me)
I suddenly had this thought...
for the first time ever.
I want a son like him.
Same here.
- Right? - Yes. It won't be half bad.
Even though I'm not even thinking about marriage,
I thought about how nice it'd be to have a son like him.
You never know.
He might cause troubles when we aren't watching.
- Right? We only saw the good side. - Yes.
You only saw the good side.
Okay. Never mind then.
I changed my mind.
(I Live Alone)
(Spring Comes Early)
(Si Hyeon, Little Tiger, is deep asleep.)
(Alarm wakes her up.)
(Stretching)
Will she go fishing at 5am?
Fishing?
You only see through the lens of your interest.
Golfers will say, "Will she have a round of golf?"
That's when I think about going to bed.
It's the perfect time for meeting Mr. Ito Junji.
It isn't her home.
The bed looks different.
You're right. That's the lodging I go to all the time.
That looks amazing.
(Where is she?)
This is Tongyeong.
Tongyeong. It's a nice place.
Tongyeong is amazing.
Tongyeong is incredible.
What's famous in Tongyeong?
Tongyeong is famous for gimbap and oysters.
The Battle of Hansan Island.
That's right.
- Did that happen in Tongyeong? - Yes.
- There are statues... - That's right.
- and the Turtle Ship. - That's right.
That's why their gimbap is called Chungmu gimbap.
- Yi Sun Sin's title, Chungmugong. - Is that where it gets the name?
Really?
- There's also honey bread. - That's right.
- Right? Honey bread. - Yes.
Ji Hyeon knows everything about the south.
I know everything.
(He's from Mokpo.)
(Proud)
It's so sunny.
(Compared to Seoul, Tongyeong is 5°C warmer.)
Since it's in the south,
it welcomes spring two weeks earlier than Seoul.
I'm here to enjoy early spring.
(Let's hurry up and head out.)
(The current time is 5:14am.)
It's so early.
(Walking fast)
Where is she going?
The sun is rising.
(She begins to walk faster.)
I can almost smell early morning from the video.
(She arrives at place after walking fast.)
It's so nice.
I've arrived at Seoho Market.
(A place with fresh agricultural and marine products)
Does it open so early in the morning?
Right next to the market is where they auction off...
seafood.
It begins at 4am.
Since this market is close...
- Seafood comes straight here. - Yes.
(Seaweed from the auction can be seen here and there.)
Seoho Market has produces...
grandmas have dug up in the countryside.
You need to visit early in the morning...
to get good ingredients...
before middle-aged women do.
The sellers bring...
small amount of precious ingredients...
you can't get in Seoul.
At Gyeongdong Market, you can buy...
top-quality produces.
At Seoho Market, you can buy precious ingredients...
- that won't go to Seoul. Yes. - Rare items.
You can buy such ingredients.
Be careful with your position as the greens expert.
There's someone who wants to take your position.
It's Bae In Hyuk.
- Exactly. I watched the episode. - He wants to take your spot.
- Did you watch it? - Yes.
(He established himself as the shepherd's purse expert...)
(and threatened Si Hyeon's position.)
- He recognized shepherd's purse. - I watched it.
- Can you do that? - Of course.
So there can be a competition with vegetables.
Of course.
I don't want to lose when it comes to vegetables.
Hello.
(The Little Tiger hunts for rare vegetables again today.)
Where are you from?
- I'm from Seoul. - Pardon?
- I'm from Seoul. - I see.
I'll get five dollars worth of this.
It's 3 dollars for 1.
It's 3 dollars for 1?
- I'll just get 1 portion then. - Just 1?
- Yes. - It's wild-caught.
The greens of the sea are the sea vegetables.
The seaweed is literally a wet vegetable.
- Right. - Greens of the sea.
- Thank you. - Bye.
How much is it for this much sweet shrimp?
- It's 20 dollars. - It's 20 dollars?
They're really expensive in Seoul.
Can I get this one?
- This one? - Yes.
- They're delicious. - They're so sweet.
They're really good.
Gosh, they look so good.
Hello.
- Hello. - You haven't gone back yet.
Right. I came last week. I came back again this week.
- Gosh. - I came yesterday.
It isn't easy to visit Tongyeong often.
Is there a reason you visit Tongyeong often?
There are many other places.
As you know, Tongyeong has...
- a lot of great seafood. - Right.
Including the salted seafood.
- Right. - Mokpo has great seafood as well.
Mokpo is great as well, but...
But the products that are produced are definitely different.
They're definitely different.
The Yellow Sea is known for its mud flat.
- Right. - Right.
Hello.
Welcome.
It's my first time seeing this.
- The hairy crab. - The hairy crab.
(She spots the hairy crab this time.)
You must have them when you visit Tongyeong.
Right.
- Is that so? - But they're hard to find.
- They're hard to find. - They aren't sold all the time.
They must be bought whenever you see them.
How do hairy crabs taste different?
For me, the meat felt really soft.
Right. The meat is really sweet as well.
Right.
I think I've only tried them marinated.
Hairy crabs are quite small.
- Right. - It's hard to get their meat.
That is why they are often marinated.
The innards taste so good.
- Right. - Right.
The savory taste is enough to kill.
I've tried hairy crabs in Japan.
But there was something I realized for the first time there.
Koreans are the only ones to mix rice with the innards.
- Really? - Really?
To distinguish Koreans in Japan,
just look for people who are mixing rice with innards.
Koreans are the only ones to do that.
That's a must when eating crabs.
Awesome.
- I'll take all of them. - Yes?
- Would you like all of them? - Yes.
- Gosh. - She's buying a lot.
That and the sea cucumbers.
Sea cucumbers.
I'll get the clam meat as well.
- I'll get some oysters as well. - Oysters?
(She spends more on seafood.)
The big ones would be great.
(Cute)
The sargassum is nowhere to be seen.
- Sorry? - The sargassum.
The sargassum?
- I wanted to get some sargassum. - What is the sargassum?
The sargassum is a sea vegetable as well.
It has these beads.
It's a sea vegetable that looks very pretty.
I saw them the week before, but I couldn't find them this week.
It was really disappointing.
Awesome. They look delicious.
(She hunts a box of different kinds of seafood.)
- Here you are. - Right.
- Thank you. - Goodbye.
She looks like someone who is doing a chore.
Hello.
(She heads somewhere with both hands full.)
Where is she going?
Nice. There's no one else.
(She arrives at a restaurant?)
Gosh!
- Hello. - Hello.
(She puts down her things on one side naturally.)
Would you like the puffer fish soup?
- Yes. - Right.
In Tongyeong,
there are famous dishes which I have for breakfast.
It's the sirak soup and the puffer fish soup.
Whenever I visited the market,
I went to this restaurant to have puffer fish soup.
The puffer fish soup must be famous.
The puffer fish soup is my favorite food.
- The puffer fish soup. - Right.
The dried radish greens soup is called the sirak soup.
Right. That's what it's called in their dialect.
- Sirak soup. - The dried radish greens soup.
In the market,
there's a separate alley for sirak soup.
The ppaettaegi porridge is sold there as well.
- Ppaettaegi porridge? - Ppaettaegi porridge?
The ppaettaegi porridge is made of sweet potato.
- Dried sweet potato. - Right.
I can sense a bit of dialect from you.
- Right. - Right.
Where are you from?
(Interested)
My parents are from Gyeongsang Province.
- I see. - My mom is from Busan...
and my dad is from Gyeongju.
- Then you're one of us. - I see.
They look so happy.
(The ones who speak in a dialect look happy.)
You two should become close friends.
- Us? - Gosh.
- We're close. - Really?
- We're really close. - Right.
The Yeongnam region and Honam region have united.
Right. That's great to see.
It's the Hwagae Market with the two of them together.
- Hwagae Market? - Hwagae Market?
Right.
- I got his autograph. - The regions have united.
The two of them could be called Hwagae Market.
- I love it. Hwagae Market. - Right.
Right. You two should release an album as Hwagae Market.
- Right. - What?
Let's do it!
Right!
(Please show your support for the new group, Hwagae Market.)
(Getting out)
(Pulling)
(She ties her hair first.)
It's her attitude toward food.
(After getting ready to welcome the food...)
- Your food is here. - Thank you.
Awesome!
(The food gets served quickly.)
- There are so many side dishes. - It's amazing, isn't it?
Why is the anchovy so big?
Tongyeong's Gijang anchovy.
Gijang anchovies are big.
The raw silver pomfret is served as a side dish.
(Even the raw silver pomfret gets served.)
(The deeply boiled puffer fish soup is the main dish.)
This is insane.
It's the best breakfast.
It's a great breakfast meal.
(It looks amazing.)
(Is she mixing the ssamjang with the chojang?)
(She takes a piece of the raw silver pomfret...)
(and dips it in the sauce she mixed together.)
(Eating)
When I eat raw fish,
I enjoy mixing up the sauces.
Right. People from the Gyeongsang Province...
eat like that.
- It's the same with sundae. - Right.
It's mostly chojang for Jeolla Province.
Right.
Even sundae is dipped in chojang.
- Right. - Right.
- Sundae dipped in chojang? - In Jeolla Province.
Cafeterias serve it like that.
- Really? - Also,
when talking with people from Busan,
they don't understand people from Seoul eating sundae with salt.
It's ssamjang no matter what for them.
Do you put in salt or sugar when having soybean noodles?
It's salt for me.
Both of them must be put in.
- Really? - You put in sugar, right?
I put in a whole bowl of sugar.
- A whole bowl? - Right.
- A whole bowl? - I put in a lot of sugar.
- You put in salt, right, Dowoon? - I don't like soybean noodles.
- That's understandable. - Right.
(She tries a spoonful of the puffer fish soup this time.)
(Slurping)
(Letting out a breath)
(This is it.)
She got touched by it.
(She grabs the vinegar all of a sudden.)
- The vinegar is placed like that. - Right.
Vinegar is added to the soup?
When a few drops of vinegar is added,
it brings up a savory taste.
It's charming how you can develop its taste.
- After eating around half of it? - Right.
After enjoying its refreshing taste.
Right.
Just like how the raw fish tastes savory...
because of the sushi rice,
the soup becomes tastier.
(Happy)
(She downs the soup from the bowl to finish off.)
The soup was so good.
(Groaning)
(Clean bowl!)
Gosh, she finished the whole bowl.
Clean bowl!
A nap would be perfect after that.
- A nap would be great. - Right.
The guys of Hwagae Market have really fallen for her.
- Right. - Right.
- That was great. - Thank you.
- I saw you on TV. - Really?
You're so pretty.
- Thank you. - She saw her on TV.
I went there really often as I'm a regular.
- She finally noticed her. - She noticed me for the first time.
- I'll come again. - Could I get a picture?
- Of course. - An autograph as well.
- I don't have an autograph. - You don't?
- You can make one today. - Sounds good.
I only signed things off when I used my card.
She's lifting her up.
I felt so embarrassed as I didn't have an autograph.
What must I do?
Sign it this way.
- I'm left-handed. - My daughter is also left-handed.
Really?
(Under the owner's lead, she tries again.)
(Looking around)
It's March 11 today.
(Thanks to the owner's perfect coaching...)
Thank you.
This is so embarrassing.
"Kim Si Hyeon was here!"
(Kim Si Hyeon was here.)
(I really enjoyed the food!)
Anyone could copy that.
Did you sign a guest book?
But I think that looks more charming.
- Really? - I like it.
(They take a picture together as well.)
Thank you.
I enjoy the food every time I come.
Thank you! It was great!
- Bye! Thank you! - Bye!
Where is she heading to now?
It doesn't seem like she will take the train back to Seoul.
(She starts running all of a sudden.)
It looks like she's running after spotting her mom.
- She looks so bright. - Right.
"Mom!"
(She runs like a child, feeling happy to see her mother.)
What is this place?
It must be a place for cooking. There are ingredients.
(She walks up naturally.)
Teacher! Hello!
Si Hyeon! What is all this?
I bought some things at the market.
- Who is it? - Who is it?
- You went to the market? - Right.
What is all this?
I bought some things at the market.
- Who is it? - Who is it?
- You went to the market? - Right.
It must be her cooking teacher.
Right.
- You came from the market? - Awesome.
There's a place like this?
(A place surrounded by all kinds of tableware and tables)
The place that I visited is the workroom of Lee Sang Hee,
a food researcher of Tongyeong food.
(He researched Tongyeong's food for around 40 years.)
(The master of Tongyeong's native food)
Food researcher?
It's still cold.
- Right. - You went to the market...
when it's still cold.
(Biting)
(Hugging)
The one next to him is his wife.
She's my favorite aunt.
I think it was when I was around 20.
I happened to visit Tongyeong.
I tried his food...
and I felt amazed by him and Tongyeong.
I got so mesmerized...
and as I wanted to learn how to make Tongyeong's food,
I went to meet him.
The food you tried was so good...
- and you decided to learn from him? - Right.
It's just like "Shota no Sushi."
- Right. - "Shota no Sushi."
- It's just like a comic book. - That was how good it was?
- That's amazing. - That's impressive.
That's the courage that comes out when you're crazy for something.
How good was it for her to be like that?
I said that I wanted to talk with him...
and asked for some of his time.
He gladly accepted me after hearing that...
I was a student learning to become a cook.
I said I wanted to follow him to the market,
so we went together the next day.
This is a picture taken by him.
I asked him to teach me how to make side dishes...
and I learned how to make Tongyeong's food from him.
- He's a great teacher. - Right.
And as time passed by,
we ended up becoming this close.
She must feel like a daughter to them.
Warm up your hands.
The things that are on the wall are all made by him.
- The sobans? - Yes.
- He studies food and culture. - Right.
Soban?
- What is a soban? - Soban?
Isn't it a bowl?
- A small bowl? - I think so.
You should ask.
Hurry up and ask.
What are sobans?
- Sobans... - What?
are the small tables that are on the wall.
Those are traditional sobans.
Have you not heard of dog-legged sobans?
- No. - The dog-legged ones.
Kian84 wanted me to ask.
(Kian84 wanted me to ask.)
They're those small tables.
You can't say that, you punk!
(Embarrassed)
Since you were coming,
I was planning to dig out some siler divaricata.
- That sounds great. - I was planning to do that.
They'll head to dig out vegetables?
They will dig them out?
- Shall we head out? - Yes.
You punk.
- There's an actual beast. - Right.
That cat was also abandoned.
(My goodness!)
The cat found a great place to stay. There must be great food there.
Let's get going.
I want to go out to dig out vegetables.
I should be able to distinguish the vegetables well.
Don't worry. Once you get there,
you will tell right away as you've studied them.
Right.
(After driving past Tongyeong's sea...)
Gosh, that's great.
It's this field.
- There are vegetables here. - I love it!
Awesome!
- A vegetable garden? - Yes.
(They arrive at the spot.)
Gosh, it's amazing!
- It's like a work of art. - That's what Tongyeong is about.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Is that a seaweed farm?
That must be for either oysters or mussels.
- The view is amazing. - Right? It's amazing, right?
- There are many fishing boats. - You want to go fishing, right?
I know, of course.
I've been out fishing before as well.
It's close to Geoje.
(Laughing)
He looks so happy.
(It's great to see the sea of Gyeongsang Province.)
A friend of mine raises vegetables here.
- Awesome. Shall we go down? - Let's go down.
The vegetables must feel nervous.
- Death is right at their doorstep. - Right.
- Their hair will be pulled out. - It might happen any second.
(Watch out for your hair.)
- Look here, Si Hyeon. - Right.
Be careful as it's slippery.
- You see the clam shells, right? - Yes.
All of these are used as fertilizers without being thrown out.
- Really? - They are used as fertilizers.
- Clam shells? - Right.
So that is why they are found in places like that.
Right.
I always thought those places were beaches in the past.
What?
Then, trilobites from the past would be found as well.
Clam shells could be found like that in the countryside.
- They're all brought over. - Right.
I see.
- This is the leaf mustard. - This is the leaf mustard.
- Leaf mustard? - Leaf mustard.
- For leaf mustard kimchi. - Leaf mustard kimchi?
- It's made from that? - I see.
- Really? - This is the green leaf mustard.
The red leaf mustard is often used.
- The red ones. - Yeosu's leaf mustard kimchi...
- is made with the red leaf mustard. - Right.
All of those look precious after knowing about them.
Exactly. We would've just trampled over them.
Right. We would've just trampled over them.
Open your eyes wide and this place is full of treasure.
Right.
This place is great.
We have to know what's what for it to be treasure.
- You see the meogu, right? - Right.
- The meogu. - These are all meogu leaves.
- They noticed right away. - Right.
- I can't tell at all. - I can't tell at all.
- Are they butterbur leaves? - Meogu leaves.
Butterbur leaves are called meogu leaves in the dialect.
- So those are butterbur leaves. - Right.
- No one knew. - They're good.
- They just look like fallen leaves. - They don't taste bitter.
How can you call them fallen leaves?
Seafood is all you know about.
- Seafood is all you know about. - But...
they look like ginkgo leaves.
Right.
- Are they good for anything? - Good for anything?
- It's probably blood circulation. - Well...
It prevents arteriosclerosis...
- and it's good for antioxidation. - Antioxidation?
(The messenger of spring, butterbur)
(Butterbur: Antioxidation, blood sugar, blood pressure)
- It's right there! - Blood pressure regulation.
You're right. You just made a guess, didn't you?
Most of them...
- are good for the same things. - That's fascinating.
Right.
(What was that?)
(Eaten as a salad or wrap)
They taste great as wraps.
They don't taste bitter.
They can be eaten right away after being blanched.
- This is amazing. - They taste great...
in doenjang jjigae.
- How are those found? - Right.
This is amazing.
It looks like they are looking for four-leaved clovers.
It really feels like that.
- Time flies like that. - That's fine as well.
Right.
- Do you know what this is? - Which one?
A flower blossomed.
- It looks so pretty. - It's a flower.
- These come out before mugwort. - This is insane!
These come out before mugwort.
I've finally got my hands on this.
It's the henbit. It's the one I looked for...
- in Gyeongdong Market. - The henbit.
The henbit?
Right.
(The vegetable she looked for in Gyeongdong Market...)
(last winter!)
(Henbit: Antioxidation, hemostatic effect)
- Antioxidation again. - Antioxidation again.
I'm sure it will prevent arteriosclerosis as well.
(There's a big chance for that.)
(It's eaten as a salad or put in doenjang soup.)
Gosh, that must be delicious!
- Doenjang soup? - In doenjang soup.
(It's eaten as a salad or put in doenjang soup.)
It's so pretty.
This one feels different.
(She uses it as an accessory.)
I wonder it's called the clown vegetable in Korean.
As the flower looks so pretty,
- it was given that name. - As it resembles a clown?
- That's how I know it. - As it's very flashy?
(A name given because of its beautiful flower!)
I wish to have a garden just like this.
I've tried digging out vegetables at a place planted with crops,
but it's my first time experiencing
a wild field where things are grown randomly.
It was a fascinating experience.
(They move to the second spot.)
- Awesome! - Here.
- They don't grow in big fields. - What's that?
- What is that? - The siler divaricata?
They grow naturally like this.
- Last year, it started growing. - It's the siler divaricata.
You know so much!
The siler divaricata?
(Siler divaricata: A vegetable that prevents winds)
It prevents winds?
- That's why it's called fang feng. - It prevents winds.
- It prevents winds. - That's how it got that name.
Fang feng.
(Blanched or mixed as a salad)
- Gosh, that looks good! - Right.
- We must have tried it. - Right.
We would've tried it without knowing what it is.
We would've all tried that.
Goats know what tastes good. Check the scent.
(She takes a bite of the freshly picked siler divaricata.)
The scent can be felt right away.
- I love its slightly tough texture. - It's so good.
- Right. - Awesome!
It's hard to find this kind of siler divaricata.
(The taste of the siler in season makes her exclaim right away.)
Hello!
- Welcome. - Greet her.
It's the owner of the vegetable garden.
(The owner allowed them to dig out the vegetables.)
We'll dig out some of the spinach.
Dig out the big ones as much as you want.
The spinach.
These taste good.
(They start hunting for the spinach raised in the sea breeze.)
Check out the roots.
- I can tell those right away. - Right.
- Those are seen often. - The roots look familiar.
- They're so pretty. - Right.
(Her hands keep moving at the sight of the appetizing color of pink.)
I want to live like this in the countryside.
- Let's get just what we need. - Right.
It will never end when we start getting greedy.
Right. I'm starting to get greedy here.
Let's get just what we need for the day.
You start to get greedy and move all around, right?
(Just enough for today!)
You can pick out some of the crown daisy greens as well.
The crown daisy greens?
The crown daisy greens are good.
- Want some crown daisy greens? - Sounds good.
Let's head over to the crown daisy greens.
- What? - What?
- Let's have these. - Gosh!
Check out the scent.
(The green crown daisy greens have grown together nicely.)
They're the crown daisy greens raised under a pine tree.
Crown daisy greens.
The crown daisy greens look really nice.
- Could you move over a little bit? - Right.
I got greedy.
(I'm sorry.)
They taste great.
There's so much.
- But that's too much. - No, it's not.
You see, I like crown daisy.
- It seems he's greedier. - You're right.
(Joking)
Gosh, look over here.
I love it.
I think that's enough.
He's fast.
(He's suddenly gotten quicker.)
(The master who taught her...)
(not to be greedy and get only what she needed...)
Wait a little longer.
(Disarmed in front of crown daisy)
I can't even see his face because he keeps digging it up.
It looks like he's been waiting for that day only.
I went back the next week,
- and they grew so much. - They grew again?
So he covered them to use as fertilizer.
Oh, you need to harvest them fast.
Yes, so it was right of him to harvest when they were good.
You need to harvest them in time.
I thought you were going to harvest only as much as you need,
- but you keep going. - What do I do?
I shouldn't be greedy.
You're not practicing what you're saying.
No, I'm just picking them.
It's so funny.
Who knows when I'll come back?
(They continued to pick...)
(the vegetables they needed for the day.)
- I feel rich. - I know. It's amazing.
This is it.
How much of crown daisy did you pick?
It looks like you picked more than a water deer would.
I thought he said he was picking enough for the day.
I wish I could pick more.
He wishes he could pick more?
Let's come back again.
I'll come back in April...
- to pick yuzu leaves. - Let's do that.
(Promising to come back next time, although they're disappointed)
Let's go back.
(Quickly returning)
It's a little embarrassing, though.
(Laughing)
It's not like we bought it.
Still, it's nice.
He seems genuinely happy.
Tell your aunt. She won't come back...
- once she goes. - It's really amazing.
- There were so many crown daisies. - I'll put my clothes away first.
She's surprised.
Try this.
(What they harvested for the day makes her jaw drop.)
- He harvested so much. - I know.
(Heading to the kitchen with the seafood...)
(she bought early in the morning)
I brought this down.
Well done.
Let's do it quickly.
Amazing.
Would you blanch spinach first?
I'm already boiling water.
(Perfectly coordinated)
The ones we harvested earlier are really nice.
Let's try making that today.
Siler divaricata tangpyeongchae.
- Tangpyeongchae? - Goodness.
Tangpyeongchae?
Usually, tangpyeongchae is made...
with mung bean jelly.
- That's the dish. - Oh, that?
It's a dish that originated from...
- That's right. - "Tangpyeongchaek."
It's called tangpyeongchae because there are various ingredients.
To gather them together and mix well.
"Tangpyeongchaek" means to recruit talented individuals fairly.
There's an even amount of various ingredients.
In Tongyeong, they add...
various seafood that goes well with siler divaricata,
so that the dish becomes more valuable.
That's the kind of dish it is.
Today, we're making siler divaricata tangpyeongchae...
and seolchi soup with seasoned vegetables.
- Seolchi soup? - Seolchi soup?
"Seolchi" means...
"to mix."
It's a soup that mixes seaweed...
and vegetables from land.
The most similar dish is radish soup.
- It's Gyeongsang's style, - I know radish soup.
but it doesn't have as much broth as radish soup.
It's slightly soupy,
so it's called seolchi soup with seasoned vegetables...
- With seasoned vegetables? - or just seolchi soup.
That's how it's called.
Let's use seasoned fish-meat paste for soy sauce today.
All right.
Seasoned fish-meat paste?
Gosh, it's warm here too.
(Striding to the rooftop)
It's so nice.
(Filled with pastes made with decades of effort)
It's his treasure.
(The master's treasure rooftop)
The codfish is dried well, right?
- So he dried codfish. - It's well-dried, seriously.
Here.
- The codfish is huge. - This is incredible.
(Hude codfish)
The master dried them himself.
It's called medicinal codfish.
They'd collect three codfish's worth of codfish roe.
Then they'd put all of them in one codfish...
- and dry it in its stomach. - They'd ferment it.
- The stomach would burst. - If you dry this,
- Medicinal codfish. - it's really delicious.
I told you I made this last time.
(Let's check this one too.)
This time...
(Soy sauce made with dried codfish)
Soy sauce made with codfish?
(Fascinated)
- It's clear. - I can't even imagine...
how such things are made.
- Its taste... - It looks delicious.
- It's making me salivate. - I know.
This is the one you made last year.
We can scoop this.
- Scoop only the clear part. - Okay.
- Scoop it slowly. - There was soy sauce...
- that I made last year. - Just the clear part.
Does it taste more savory?
Totally. It's like a combination...
of fish sauce and soy sauce.
- This much? - Yes, that much is good.
Let's bring it down.
(Taking only enough for cooking and heading back to the kitchen)
- It'll be delicious. - It's going to be delicious.
Si Hyeon, you should...
(Prepping ingredients in earnest)
- cut these. - Okay.
- Sea cucumber. - That looks delicious.
I'll prep one for you.
Do it like this.
(Focused)
(Unlike earlier when they were filled with laughter,)
(it's gotten more serious.)
Remove the innards.
(It's gotten more serious.)
It's different from learning from a chef in Seoul...
- and from him. - Of course.
It's a real-life lesson.
As for the local dishes,
there are so many things...
that professional chefs don't know of.
That's what I realized.
- Since it's a local cooking method. - That's right.
When you come to regions that deal with seafood mostly,
you get to learn methods that go beyond your imagination.
There are various and deeper methods...
in regions.
(I'll prep sea cucumbers this time.)
(Cutting without hesitation)
(Removing)
(Removing the innards skillfully)
(Smiling)
You're very thorough.
(Happy)
(Thoroughly prepping sea cucumbers)
Si Hyeon, you're good.
- It's torn. - Your training is complete.
"There's nothing more to teach."
- Is it ready? - Yes.
If the chef says so, then it's ready.
- Those who can't eat it can eat it. - You blanch it.
Oh, it's slightly blanched.
It becomes really firm and crunchy.
Si Hyeon, you'll make seasoned radish.
- Oysters? - Try stir-frying oysters.
- Do I use this? All of them? - Put all of them in.
If you stir-fry it slightly with sesame oil,
its natural odor will be gone.
Add radish around now and stir-fry them together.
(Pouring julienned radish)
Almost all dishes from Tongyeong...
use broth from stir-fried diced seafood...
to stir-fry seasoned vegetables.
We stir-fried radish to use as the base for seolchi soup.
That's what we're doing.
- So you use that broth. - Yes.
That's because oyster isn't rare there.
- They brim with oysters. - And it's delicious.
(Pouring fish-meat soy sauce they got from the crock)
In any case, it's good if it makes broth. Done.
(It'll be done if you wait until oyster and radish mix well.)
Anything made in that pot is good.
Exactly.
That's done. Now, let's steam hairy crabs.
- Like this. - Flip them.
(Tongyeong's seasonal ingredients are being prepped one by one.)
- So they're being steamed. - Oh, the crabs from earlier?
After cleaning the live ones.
(The seasonal hairy crabs from Tongyeong's ocean...)
- Should I open it? - Yes. I bet they're all cooked.
- They look delicious. - Amazing.
It becomes softer if you steam it without the lid.
The aroma will be gone, though.
You should steam siler divaricata.
Oh, you should steam siler divaricata.
(Fragrant)
Please season seaweed and spinach.
(Adding seaweed from Tongyeong's ocean)
It must be delicious, right?
(Lightly seasoning it to prep it)
(Let's see if the radish is cooked.)
It smells delicious.
(The radish is perfectly cooked for seolchi soup.)
Gosh, it smells amazing.
(Striding up to the lab)
(Struggling)
It was hot, that's why.
There was no doorknob.
(Opening the door easily with quick thinking)
(Entering the lab safely)
It's only beginning now.
(Si Hyeon sets up the ingredients one by one.)
(They're ready for the culinary research in earnest.)
I'm really curious how it'll taste with hairy crabs and everything.
(Ingredients for seolchi soup and siler divaricata tangpyeongchae)
All right.
(Opening)
(Preparing her notebook before cooking)
- Is that your notepad? - Yes.
The notebook I used to write down things.
I used it up.
Writing things down from a class...
- in a big notebook... - Oh, I see.
makes it easy to read.
That sounds like a good idea.
What shall we start with, Si Hyeon?
With seolchi soup.
(What shall we start with in earnest?)
Here's what you're going to do.
(The first dish is seolchi soup.)
You're going to season spinach.
Grab a bit of salt and season it.
Add a drop of sesame oil.
(Pouring nutty sesame oil as well)
- Mix lightly. - Yes, mix lightly.
You shouldn't mix...
baby spinach too hard.
As for seaweed, use fish-meat soy sauce instead of salt.
- Add that. - Fish-meat soy sauce.
Then add nutty sesame oil and sesame.
Si Hyeon, mix it in a ratio that you think seems right.
(Let's add it to the seasoned radish that you cooked earlier.)
(Adding seasoned spinach on top of seasoned radish)
Mix it gently so they won't crumble.
It was my first time cooking like that.
- This much? - You can add more.
As long as it's delicious.
They don't need to be in a perfect ratio.
It's seolchi soup, right?
So add more water so it becomes more watery.
This much. Then mix it.
(You add water to that?)
- Was it good? - It was really good.
It looks delicious.
It's neither gukbap nor seasoned vegetables.
Exactly.
It's a strange dish. You can even mix rice in it.
It becomes more delicious because of the carbs from rice.
It must have the scents from both mountains and ocean.
Yes. That's why it's called seolchi soup.
- "To mix?" - Yes.
Siler divaricata tangpyeongchae.
What should you add for the base of its taste?
- The crabs. - The crabs.
Now, pick out the crab meat.
That's really delicious.
There's juice inside.
We're going to mix the vegetables with this last.
- Imagine how delicious it'd be. - It must be delicious.
Collect it separately.
We're going to mix the vegetables with this last.
It must be so good.
Goodness. We add hairy crabs...
and the umami-rich crab juice.
Gosh, it must be delicious.
(Mixing with crab meat and innards)
To this, we'll add...
the shrimp and clams we prepared.
(The clams, shrimp, and oysters they stir-fried in advance)
So many ingredients and so much effort are added.
Add about this much.
Did they imagine...
they'd meet like that when they were alive?
- They'd never run into each other. - They must've had no idea.
Then add a bit of sesame oil.
You wouldn't be able to find this on a delivery app.
- I should visit Tongyeong. - The plating is nice.
I'm grateful that you showed this to us.
I wouldn't have known this dish until I died...
if you hadn't shown it to us.
- We'd have never known. - Right?
- Did you make them deliciously? - Yes.
Can I taste it?
- Yes, try that. - Of course.
You should have it with the soup.
(Taking a bite)
(How is it?)
Is it good?
Bring me rice.
"Bring me rice."
(Laughing)
- That's the best compliment. - You're right.
It's so good.
- I can't imagine its taste. - It's really good.
- How does it taste? - It is hard to imagine.
- It's a little hard to describe. - What does it taste like?
When they hold ancestral rites in Gyeongsang Province,
they serve radish soup.
- It has shrimp, clams, squid, - That's right.
and all sorts of seafood. There's radish soup like that.
They also serve seasoned seaweed.
You add all of them with rice.
Oh, that's how it tastes?
You can taste the radish from the radish soup...
and seasoned seaweed as well.
And the base is the radish soup?
- The base taste? - That's the taste.
It tastes like the soup from radish soup.
The taste from seafood radish soup...
- It's a little salty and... - Right? It's hard, right?
- I mean, I can't... - Their expressions were like...
It's hard to imagine for a man from Mokpo.
Oh, you don't hold ancestral rites?
It's hard for a man from Mokpo.
What's radish soup again?
You've never had radish soup?
- Radish soup... - You sure you're from Gyeongsang?
- I go to church, that's why. - People from there...
You only acted like you're from Busan.
(Joking)
I did live there.
You're a savvy Seoulite.
(It turns out he's a savvy Seoulite.)
Try the sea cucumber too. That's it.
(Trying a bite of siler divaricata tangpyeongchae as well)
- Siler divaricata is really sweet. - Its aroma is different.
You can actually sell this.
Yes. This is really good.
She got both compliments. "You can actually sell this."
- It's so good. - I'm going to Dongporu later.
- Are you? - Yes.
- Take this too. - I'll take this as well.
Then I will...
- It's perfect for eating alone. - It is.
(Taking her notebook out)
(She took out her notebook, seizing the chance.)
So it doesn't matter whatever ingredient I add...
to siler divaricata tangpyeongchae?
Yes, it doesn't have to be those seafood.
If you don't have hairy crabs,
you can add blue crabs.
You don't need to add sea cucumbers or crabs.
- Sea cucumbers are amazing, though. - The master...
is passing on all his knowledge.
How else do you eat sea cucumbers?
We used raw seaweed earlier after rinsing it, right?
Yes, stone seaweed.
(Her notes fill up a page in no time.)
That's a true asset.
Si Hyeon, I think you'll do well.
Thank you.
When I saw you mixing vegetables earlier,
I noticed that you could do it.
Some people mix them too hard.
It's just that you find whatever Si Hyeon does adorable.
You're not satisfied with whatever others do.
This is why I like coming to Tongyeong.
Is that so?
I agree.
The master dyed the wrapping cloth himself.
It's so pretty.
- Go on. - All right.
Let me hug you one last time.
(Let me hug you one last time, Si Hyeon.)
- Work hard, okay? - Okay.
- Don't lose your original spirit. - Studying is the only way.
(Okay!)
- Thank you. - Sure.
Thank you for this.
Her clip keeps feeling like a comic.
- I know. It does to me too. - Really?
You're like a real family.
Of course.
(She left after saying goodbye to her master sadly.)
(She trudges along somewhere like she's used to.)
Hello. I'd like it to go, please.
(She buys Chungmu gimbap as a takeaway order.)
- She got Chungmu gimbap. - Thank you.
That's my favorite place.
Have a good day.
(Then she sets off busily.)
- You must be eating it somewhere. - That's right.
(Gazing)
The weather was amazing.
You must be eating it on the turtle ship.
(Instead of the turtle ship, she sits on the bench in front.)
(Taking something out)
(She took out ice cream to recharge with sugar.)
I'm low on sugar.
(Taking a big scoop)
(Eating)
That must be good.
It was really good.
Oh, it's mochi.
(Mouth filled with chewiness)
The mochi is crazy delicious.
(Taking another bite)
Eating something sweet really hits the spot.
I was really low on sugar then.
(Finding her cute)
(Putting the empty cup back into the plastic bag)
(Let's go.)
(Setting off again now that she's refuelled with sugar)
The weather is amazing.
(Charming alleyway, Dongpirang)
Wait. It's Dongpirang.
It looks like a duck.
(The place she hurriedly got to)
Dongporu?
- Dongporu is... - It's pretty!
a gazebo on top of Dongpirang.
You can see the whole Tongyeong at once there.
I like the view that helps you clear your mind,
the pleasant wind,
and the quietness of the gazebo.
I always stop by Dongporu when the weather is nice.
(She takes out Chungmu gimbap as soon as she arrives.)
It's really simple, but it's delicious.
- I know. - It's really good.
It's only good when you eat it there.
- That's right. - From what I know,
Chungmu gimbap is what sailors ate...
- That's right. - because it wouldn't be spoiled.
That's what they chose.
Doesn't gimbap go bad really fast when it's outside?
- It doesn't have pickled radish. - That's right.
- Chungmu gimbap doesn't have it. - It has only rice and...
Oh, it's the filling that goes bad.
It's like fast food for sailors.
(I see.)
It has only rice and seasoned squid on the side.
I'm learning a lot today.
(This is fun.)
(She's done setting everything up to eat conveniently.)
- Gosh. - Gosh, it's driving me crazy.
- It looks so good. - I must go to Tongyeong.
(Siler divaricata tangpyeongchae and seolchi soup...)
(that resembles Tongyeong's nature)
They look so good.
(Grabbing seolchi soup first)
(It's indeed good.)
I should have this soup on my birthday.
It feels strange to see her eat with that flag.
It looks like I conquered the city.
- Like a general's daughter. - She took over Tongyeong.
(The baby general who conquered Tongyeong's seasoned vegetables)
(This time, she takes a bite to take over Chungmu gimbap.)
(She takes a bite of spicy seokbakji right away.)
- That must be good. - It really is good. Gosh.
That's really good.
(Staring)
The view is to die for.
The view is amazing too.
(She eats up siler divaricata tangpyeongchae...)
(after seeing the ocean.)
(Then she stares at the ocean again.)
Gosh, it's lovely.
Gosh.
I'm so serious about Tongyeong, and I go there so often.
People around me call me the daughter of Tongyeong too.
That's how much I love Tongyeong.
It helped me clear my mind,
and I got to smell the vegetables and pick them happily.
I felt rich after picking a basket of them.
It's like a haven for my heart.
I get no stress whenever I go to Tongyeong,
and I become relaxed.
It's like a hometown I go to whenever I'm struggling.
Siler divaricata is a bit bitter,
but the sea cucumber's sweetness dialed it down.
- You constantly study. - Yes.
(Returned to the Home of My Heart)
(Next story)
(Clicking)
(Wilson is here.)
(She's been living alone for 14 years.)
(It's Comedian Kim Shin Young.)
(Welcome to Shin Young's world.)
(The maximalist's taste is reflected here and there.)
(A denim room)
(And a shoes room)
(There's even a dressing room that looks like a maze.)
(If I sell them all, I can buy this place.)
(Heading straight to the rice cooker as soon as she gets up?)
(In the morning, she has the peak appetite.)
(She starts with slurping noodles.)
(A perfectly customized meal course for herself)
(Wrapping up with seaweed tea for her health)
(Gosh, this is nice.)
(An extreme homebody's routine)
(Why wouldn't it work?)
(I have so much to do today!)
Goodness.
(An alarm rang!)
(Since she needs to fill her off-day with happiness...)
This is perfect.
(The last alarm of the day comes from her stomach.)
(Perfect timing)
(Perfect seasoning)
(A Perfect Day)
(An Almost Perfect Day)
(Neat outfit, neat hair)
(And a mysteriously big bag?)
(Woo Il is heading somewhere excitedly.)
(Today is an especially important day.)
(Where did Woo Il who dressed up extra nice head to?)
(It's a cooking class he's been going to frequently recently.)
(He got through the past days with simple meals.)
(Investing in today's meal and future jobs)
(He's been working hard constantly...)
(for a long time.)
(Seriously passionate without trying to be funny)
(Why did you soak the potatoes in water?)
(Passion for learning boiling over)
(Confidence built up step by step)
(Let's go for it again today.)
(Cut the cartilage only.)
(Like this?)
(I don't think it has cartilage.)
(Yes, it does.)
(Embarrassed)
(Please prepare starch water.)
(Grease it again.)
(Flustering about due to a series of missions)
(Please wrap it up in 10 minutes.)
(On top of everything, he's pressed for time.)
(Let's hurry up.)
(A huge mistake)
(What's wrong with me today?)
(Nothing Seems to be Easy)